你怎么...怎么拿到的
How did you... how did you get this?
从你同事那拿的
From your coworker.
反对  法官阁下  那是什么文件
Objection, Your Honor. What is this document?
根据那位律师刚刚说的
Uh, well, from what the counselor just told us
应该是条短信吧
it seems to be a text message.
而且看来  你的证人认出了这条短信
And from all appearances, your witness recognizes it.
所以你的反对理由是什么
So what is the objection?
没有根据
Foundation.
是啊  这也是个反对理由
Sure. That's an objection.
反对无效
Overruled.
你能读一下短信吗
Could you read the text message?
「我的错  得赶紧告诉NG
Um, "My bad. Gotta tell NG.
NG会杀了我的」
NG will kill me."
NG指尼尔·格罗斯
NG being Neil Gross?
是的
Yeah.
你是不是编造了这起偷窃事件
Didn't you fabricate the whole theft story
因为你害怕尼尔·格罗斯会杀了你
because you were afraid NG might kill you?